If you do not resist,
（レム）
抵抗しないで
くれたら―
I can grant you a painless death.
楽に終わりにしてあげることも
できますよ
Why are you doing this?
（ナツキ･スバル）
どうして こんなことを…
That's a pretty clichéd line,
but do you mind my asking?
って ありきたりなセリフ
言っていいか？
Punish those who seem suspicious.
疑わしきは罰せよ
メイドとしての心得です
It's a principle of all maids.
Does Ram know?
ラムは知ってんのか
I intend to finish this
before my sister sees anything.
姉様に見られる前に
終わらせるつもりです
Is that really how little you trusted me?
そんなに 俺が
信用できなかったのか
はい
Yes.
Damn, I'm stupid.
ざまあねえ 俺
I was so sure we were getting along well.
うまくやってたなって
勘違いしやがって
My sister—
姉様は…
I don't wanna hear it!
（スバル）
聞きたくねえよ！
Take this!
（スバル）くらえ！
（シャッター音）
ハア ハア ハア ハア…
おわっ！
足がー！ あああっ
My leg!
Mana of water, heal this damaged body.
（レム）
水のマナよ この者に癒やしを
If you die so easily,
こんなあっさり死なれては―
I cannot get any information from you.
聞き出すことも
聞き出せませんから
If you had stabbed me with this,
さっき レムに
これを突き立てていれば―
you could have fled a bit farther.
もう少し
逃げられたはずでしょうに
I ask you this:
お聞きします
Are you a member of a faction that
opposes Emilia-sama's bid for the throne?
あなたは エミリア様に敵対する
候補者の陣営の方ですか？
My heart belongs to Emilia-tan forever—
俺の心はいつでも
エミリアたんのものだ
Who hired you,
and under what conditions?
誰に どんな条件で
雇われているんですか
Emilia-tan's smile, and it was priceless—
（スバル）
エミリアたんの笑顔に
プライスレスで…
Are you affiliated with the Witch Cult?
あなたは―
魔女教の関係者ですか
The Witch Cult?
魔女教？
What the hell is that?
知らねえよ
My family has been secular
for generations—
そもそも うちは代々―
Don't play dumb!
（スバル）無宗教…
（レム）とぼけないでください！
Your bald-faced lies
can only take you so far,
そんなに
魔女のにおいを漂わせて―
when you're practically
drowning in the witch's stench!
無関係だなんて
白々しいにも限度がありますよ！
As I watched you
conversing with my sister,
姉様と あなたが
会話しているのを見ている時―
I felt as if I was going mad
with rage and apprehension!
レムは不安と怒りで
どうにかなってしまいそうでした
Someone associated with the one who
has caused my sister so much agony,
姉様をあんな目に遭わせた元凶が
その関係者が―
boldly encroaching
on the place we call ours...
のうのうと レムと姉様の
大事な居場所に
I cannot bear it any longer.
もう 耐えられないんです
Even if I know my sister is only acting friendly
and pretending to care for you!
姉様が世話をするのを装って―
あなたと親しげに―
ふるまっているだけと
知っていても！
I don't cut my hands
when I peel vegetables anymore.
（スバル）
野菜の皮 むく時に
手 切らなくなったよ
I can read and write now,
even if it's just the simple stuff.
読み書き 簡単なやつだけど
できるようになったんだ
I kept my word and studied.
約束守って勉強してた
I was able to read those fairy tales.
童話 読めたんだぜ
All thanks to you two.
お前たちのおかげで
What are you talking about?
何を 言っているんですか
I'm talking about the things you guys gave me.
お前たちが
俺にくれたものの話だよ
I have no memory of any of that.
そんなこと 記憶にありません
Why don't you remember!?
何で… 覚えてねんだよ！
Why do you all keep leaving me behind!?
どうして みんなでよってたかって
俺を置いていくんだよ！
What did I do!?
俺が何したっつんだよ！
What am I supposed to do!?
俺に何しろってんだよ！
何がいけねえんだよ！
Where did I go wrong!?
Why do you two hate me so much!?
お前ら どうしてそんなに
俺を憎むんだよ！
You even said you'd cut my hair for me...
髪を切る約束だって―
All this time, I've...
俺はずっと…
（レム）レムは
I...
I've loved you both so m—
俺はお前らのこと だ…
My sister is too kind for her own good.
（レム）
姉様は優しすぎます
Sir, have you awakened?
（レム）
お客様 お目覚めですか？
（ラム）
お客様 起きてたの？
Sir, you're awake?
Subaru, Ram and Rem were really worried.
（エミリア）
スバル ラムとレムの２人が
すごーく心配してたわよ
They were unusually despondent,
wondering if they'd been impolite.
何か失礼があったかもって
珍しく落ち込んで…
（スバル）
何もなかったよ
Nothing happened...
between them and me.
俺と あの２人の間には
Subaru, are you all right?
スバル？ 大丈夫？
If something's wrong,
何かあるなら
私でよければ相談に乗るけど
you're welcome to talk to me.
If only I could tell Emilia that I can't
do this anymore, that I'm at my wit's end.
（スバル）
もうダメだよ
俺 限界なんだって
エミリアに言えたら…
あっ そうだよ
That's it.
What?
（エミリア）何？
So far, I've been struggling
to change things alone, but...
（スバル）
今まで俺は 全て自分だけで
変えようとあがいていた
だが…
Subaru, are you sure you're all right?
スバル 本当に大丈夫？
エミリアに聞いてほしいことがある
There's something I want you to know.
はい
Okay.
Emilia...
（スバル）
エミリア 俺は今まで―
Up until now,
I've died several ti—
何度も死に…
Whoa... Wait!
（スバル）おい… 待て…
This is no laughing matter!
それは本気でシャレにならねえ…
ぐおっ ああああ…
Subaru?
（エミリア）スバル？
（スバル）ああ！ あっ
Subaru!
スバル！
What's come over you all of a sudden?
どうしたの 急に
（スバル）
体は動く 声も出る
心臓も痛くない
My body moves.
My voice works.
My heart doesn't hurt.
But...
だが―
恐怖は刻まれた
The fear etched into me is all too real.
どうしたの？
さっきから本当に変よ
What's wrong?
You've been acting really strange.
Subaru, if something's going on—
スバル 何かあるなら…
I have a favor to ask.
（スバル）頼みがあるんだ
Of course.
Have nothing to do with me.
俺に 構わないでくれ
I can't tell anyone about Return by Death.
（スバル）
死に戻りを
打ち明けることは許されない
I've died in this mansion three times.
この屋敷で 俺は３度死んだ
Back in the capital, I didn't die a fourth time.
４度目の死は
王都でも経験していない
For all I know, if I die again,
もし 次に死ねば―
there might not be a next time.
戻れないかもしれない
I suppose that's quite
a cowardly look you're wearing.
（ベアトリス）
随分と ふぬけたツラ構えに
なっているかしら
Why are you here?
（スバル）何しに来たんだ
Bubby and that child told me
to come check on you.
にーちゃと
あの小娘に言われて―
ツラを見にきてやったのよ
パックとエミリア
Puck and Emilia?
Since you were acting strangely,
お前の様子がおかしいから―
I suppose they suspected I did something
to you when you first woke up.
最初に目覚めた時に ベティーが
何かしたんじゃないかって―
疑ってるかしら
Talk about rude!
失礼な話なのよ
I get it. I'm okay now.
分かった もう大丈夫だ
You came to apologize.
お前は謝りにきてくれた
それで十分だよ
That's enough for me.
I suppose you believe I have reason
to apologize to you?
どうして ベティーが
謝らなくちゃならないのかしら！
I can't leave until I correct that notion.
まず そこを訂正しないと
帰るに帰れないのよ
Not only do you look gloomy,
ツラが辛気臭くなった
だけじゃなく―
but you smell even worse than before.
随分と濃くなっているのかしら
Huh?
You reek of the witch.
魔女のにおいなのよ
鼻が曲がりそうかしら
I suppose it feels like it's burning my nose.
Witch? You mean the Witch of Envy?
魔女って 嫉妬の魔女か
What else in the world would someone mean
when they bring up a witch?
今の世界で 魔女と言われて
それ以外の何がありえるのよ
Why do you smell her on me?
どうして そのにおいを
俺から感じる？
Who knows?
さあ 何にせよ―
Regardless, as someone who has earned her favoritism, you're a burden.
魔女から特別な扱いを受ける
お前はやっかい者なのよ
It's not too comforting to hear I'm getting
favoritism from someone I know nothing about.
顔も名前も知らない相手に
特別扱いってのは ゾッとしねえな
If you have nothing to say, I'm leaving.
何もないなら もう行くのよ
I suppose I'll let Bubby know what you told me.
にーちゃには ちゃんと
話したことは伝えておくのかしら
Wait a minute!
ちょっと待て お前
俺に悪いと思ってんだよな？
You feel sorry for what you did to me, right?
（ベアトリス）思ってないのよ
I do not.
I'm telling Puck!
（スバル）
パックに言いつけんぞ
Well, I suppose I might feel
the tiniest little bit sorry.
すこーしだけ 思ってることも
あるかもしれないかしら
If you regret what you did
and want my forgiveness,
悪いと思ってて
許してほしけりゃ―
I want you to do me one favor.
１個だけ 俺の願いを聞いてくれ
Let's hear it.
（ベアトリス）言ってみるのよ
Until the fifth morning...
５日目の朝 あさっての朝だ
The day after tomorrow, that is.
Would you keep me safe until then?
その時間まで
俺を守ってくれないか
I suppose I won't condone you
bringing dissension into this mansion.
（ベアトリス）
もめ事を持ち込まれるのは
ごめんなのかしら
This place is vitally important to me.
ベティーにとって この屋敷は
無くてはならない場所なのよ
I have no intention of doing anything.
（スバル）
俺のほうから何かする気はない
I just want to stop any sparks from flying.
かかる火の粉を払いたいだけだ
I suppose that's quite an admirable motive
for one who leaves even that in the hands of others.
それさえ他人任せなくせに
随分と立派な志なのかしら
For once, I have no comeback to that.
今回に限っちゃ
返す言葉もねえよ…
ハア
Hold out your hand.
手 出すのよ
I shall grant your wish.
汝(なんじ)の願いを聞き届ける
I, Beatrice, on my honor,
am henceforth bound by this contract.
ベアトリスの名において
契約はここに結ばれる
Temporary or not, a contract is a contract.
たとえ仮でも 契約は契約
I'll grant your nonsensical favor.
お前の わけの分からない頼み
聞いてやるかしら
Seriously?
マジかよ
幼女に泣かされそうになった
A little girl is gonna make me cry.
Don't call me a little girl!
幼女とか言うななのよ
Oh, and if you tell Bubby,
I suppose you'll regret it!
あと にーちゃに告げ口したら
許さないかしら フン
It's that important to you?
そんな大事か？ それ
必死さが鬼ががってんな お前
It's like you're demoniacally possessed,
with that desperation of yours.
（ベアトリス）プウ
（スバル）
ハア ハア ハア ハア…
Stop!
やめろー！
（ベアトリス）
いつまでもグースカと
寝てるんじゃないかしら
I suppose you can't keep sleeping forever.
（ベアトリス）フン
（スバル）ボンボルディア…
Bombardier!
I forced myself to come
because it's the designated time,
約束の時間だから
いやいや来てやったのに―
随分 余裕のある奴なのよ
yet you seem awfully unconcerned.
肝心の４日目に居眠りとか
マジで命知らずのアホか 俺
Falling asleep on the fourth day?
What kind of reckless idiot am I?
I suppose you should quit your grumbling.
（ベアトリス）
ブツブツとうるさいかしら
いいから 適当なとこに
掛けているのよ
Go ahead and sit wherever you want.
The forbidden library?
（スバル）禁書庫
Did you carry me in here while I slept?
寝てる間に
俺を担ぎこんだのか
I suppose I'd rather not stick around
in that room rife with your stench.
お前のにおいが充満してる部屋で
過ごすなんて ごめんかしら
The forbidden library is the only place for me.
ベティーの居場所は
禁書庫だけなのよ
I suppose you need
to observe proper manners.
お前もお行儀よくしているかしら
Beatrice, I'm sure I'm wrong,
ベアトリス
まさかとは思うけど―
寝てる俺の手とか
握ってなかったよな？
but you didn't hold my hands
while I was asleep, did you?
You are quite wrong, indeed.
ホントにまさかなのよ
I suppose I'd refuse to do
that even at Bubby's request.
仮に にーちゃのお願いでも
断らせてもらうかしら
Flat-out denial, huh?
断言かよ
お行儀よくって言われてもなあ…
I'm not sure what you mean
by "proper manners," though.
あっ なあ お前それで…
So hey, are you—
You're annoying me with all your questions!
（ベアトリス）
質問ばかりで 小うるさいのよ
I suppose I'd like for you to remain silent.
少し黙っているがいいかしら
A summons.
呼んでる
Huh?
I suppose my presence is required.
（ベアトリス）
呼ばれているかしら
Oh, right. You're here.
I suppose I forgot.
ああ そう言えばいたのよ
忘れてたかしら
H-Hey, hold on!
（スバル）
おっ おい 待てよ
今 外に出たら…
If you go out there now...
Stay here if you want. I don't care.
（ベアトリス）
引っこんでいても構わないのよ
ここにいれば安全かしら
I suppose you'll be safe here.
Damn it! What the hell is this?
ああ クソ 何だってんだよ
Did I...
まさか… 越えたのか
４日目の夜を
make it through the fourth night?
あれだけ
遠いって思いこんでたのに
And I thought it was so far away.
こんなにあっさりと
But here I am. Just like that.
Subaru?
（エミリア）スバル
（スバル）あ…
Emilia?
（スバル）エミリア
Subaru, where have you been?
スバル どこに行ってたの？
Oh, I was just...
（スバル）あっ いや… 俺は
You know...
だって… ううん いいの
No, never mind.
Come with me.
いいから 一緒に来て
Huh? Where are we going?
え？ どこ行くんだよ
エミリアたん？
Emilia-tan?
What's with the face you're making?
何でそんな顔してるんだよ
Everything will be fine now.
だってもう 全部うまくいく
そうだろう？
Right? I'm alive, and you're...
俺がこうして無事で
エミリアも
Oh, I know! Let's go to the village!
あっ そうだ
村にさ 一緒に行こう
There's so much I want to do and tell you!
やりたいこと 話したいこと
いっぱいあるんだ
So much has happened!
いっぱいあったんだよ
Subaru...
（エミリア）スバル
Emilia?
エミリア…
（ラム）いやあああっ！
How...
どうして…
何で レムが殺されちまってる…
Why is Rem dead?
Don't touch her!
（ラム）触らないで！
Don't touch Rem...
レムに…
ラムの妹に触らないで！
Don't touch my little sister!
（ロズワール･Ｌ･メイザース）
死因は 衰弱死だーね
眠るように命の火を消されてる
She died of weakness.
It was as if she merely fell asleep.
The method was more of a curse than a spell.
魔法より呪術よりの手法だ
I thought it was Rem who used that curse.
（スバル）
あの呪いはレムだとばっかり…
呪術師とレムは別個
So Rem isn't the shaman?
My dear guest, have you any
idea what might have occurred?
お客人 なーにか
心当たりはないかねーえ
After this has happened
to a dear member of my staff,
かわいがっていた従者が
こんな目に遭わされて―
I seem to be a little bit angry.
私も少々
気が立っているようだ
Subaru,
（エミリア）スバル
if you know anything, tell us.
何か知ってるなら 言って
I want to spill it all
and get it off my chest.
（スバル）
いっそ 洗いざらい
ぶちまけて楽になりたい
イッテ…
Ow!
If you know something, spit it out!
何か知っているなら
洗いざらい ぶちまけなさい！
Wait, Ram! That's...
（スバル）
待てラム それは…
I keep my promises.
（ベアトリス）
約束は守る主義なのよ
As long as he remains in this mansion,
屋敷にいる間は―
この男の身の安全は
ベティーが守る契約かしら
I suppose I am contracted to protect him.
Beatrice-sama?
ベアトリス様
ロズワール こいつは昨晩
禁書庫にいたかしら
Roswaal, I suppose he spent last
night in the forbidden library.
だから この一件とは
関係ないはず…
So he surely had nothing to do with—
There is no further need
to emphasize the situation at hand.
事態に重きを置くべきは
すでにそこにない
しーかし 君が身を張って
守るほどとは―
However, for you
to guard him with your life,
よーっぽど彼が
気に入ったのかな？
means you must have taken
quite a liking to him.
冗談は 化粧と
性癖だけにするかしら
I suppose you should keep the jokes
to your makeup and weird fetishes.
None of that even matters!
（ラム）
そんなの 全部どうでもいいのよ！
ジャマしないで
Get out of the way!
ラムを通して
Let me through.
レムの仇(かたき)を…
何か知っているなら全部話して
I must avenge Rem.
If you know anything, tell me!
ラムを―
Help me.
レムを―
Help Rem!
助けて
I'm sorry, Ram. Despite all this,
ごめんね ラム
私はそれでも スバルを信じてみる
I choose to trust Subaru.
Subaru, please.
スバル お願い―
If you can help Ram and Rem,
あなたがラムを レムを
救ってあげられるなら―
please do.
お願い
ごめん
I'm sorry.
（エミリア）スバルー！
Subaru!
（ラム）
絶対に殺してやるー！
I swear I'll kill you!
（スバル）逃げた
I ran.
I ran away.
俺は逃げたんだ
I ran away from them.
逃げ出しちまったんだ
もう あの場所には戻れない
I can't go back there again.
What choice did I have!? What else could I...
しかたねえじゃねえかよ！
俺に何が…
And I was...
俺だって
あんな楽しかったってのにー！
I was having so much fun too!
（スバル）
似てるな あの死に場所と
This looks like the place where I died.
Where I died?
死に場所…
If I die...
死ねば…
Will I be saved from this whole situation?
（スバル）
救われるだろうか この状況から
Of course... If I die, everything will change.
あっ そうだよな
死んじまえば変わる
（スバル）
あがいて あがいて あがき続けた
結果がこれだってんなら
If I struggled and fought so much,
only to end up here,
何の意味があるんだ
then what's the point?
崖
The cliff...
If I close my eyes and take
one step, it'll all be over.
（スバル）
このまま目をつむったまま
一歩を踏み出せば それで終わりだ
What will happen to me if I die again?
（スバル）
今度死んだら… 俺はどうなるんだ
あと たった一歩が…
It's just one step away.
I can't even...
俺はこんな―
I can't even do something so simple.
こんな簡単なことを…
I finally found you.
（ベアトリス）
ようやく見つけたのよ
（スバル）どうして
Why...
I suppose you could elaborate.
何なのかしら
Why did you come for me? I...
どうして来てくれたんだ　俺は…
お前の身の安全を守るのが
ベティーの交わした契約なのよ
The contract I entered
into was to protect you.
I thought you were only supposed to
be my bodyguard until this morning.
ボディガードは 今日の朝までって
話だったはずだが
お前の思い違いじゃないかしら
I suppose you're under
the wrong impression.
I don't remember discussing a time limit.
期限の話をした覚えはないのよ
I suppose you only cling to hope
for your own convenience.
淡い期待を抱くのは
都合がよすぎるかしら
What was lost can't be reclaimed.
（ベアトリス）
失われた者は戻らない
あの姉に弁明する
機会なんて もうない
You'll have no more chances
to explain yourself to the older sister.
You threw that away.
お前はそれを投げ捨てたのよ
どちらが欠けても
あの姉妹は もう足りないかしら
I suppose no matter which is lost,
those sisters will never be complete again.
（スバル）
俺は あの２人のことも大切で
守りたいと思ってたのに
But I cared about those two,
and I wanted to protect them!
I suppose you believe you know
something about those sisters.
（ベアトリス）
あの姉妹の何を
お前は知ってるのかしら
どちらが欠けても
もう元には戻らない
No matter which is lost,
they won't be restored to what they were.
They can't be.
戻れないのよ
So in the end,
結局 俺は
何も知らないまま―
I was just making a selfish,
disgraceful fuss in my own ignorance?
てめえ勝手に みっともなく
騒ぎ立ててただけだってのかよ
（ベアトリス）せめて―
At the very least,
目の届かない所で死んでくれないと
夢見が悪いかしら
I suppose you need to die somewhere
out of my sight, or else I'll have bad dreams.
だから お前を
領地の外へ逃がしてやるのよ
So I'll help you escape this domain.
そういえば あの時―
Come to think of it, back then,
両手を誰かが握ってくれて…
both my hands were being held.
Ram... Rem...
（スバル）ラム レム
If they couldn't bear to see me suffer,
２人が 苦しむ俺を
見てらんなくて―
and held both my hands...
両手を握って
くれていたんだとしたら
If that's the kind of people they are,
そんな奴らだったとしたら
俺は放っておけんのか
how can I leave them?
I swear I'll kill you!
（ラム）
絶対に殺してやるー！
I heard a voice seething with hatred.
（スバル）
憎悪に満ちた声を聞いた
だが それ以上に
But more than that...
（ラム）いやあああっ！
Her tearful shriek won't get out of my head.
（スバル）
あの泣き声が消えてくれない
I've always been the type that
drifts toward the easiest path.
もともと 俺は―
楽なほうへ楽なほうへ
流されやすいタチなんだ
Hey, Subaru, you're thinking
about something pretty stupid.
おい バカなこと考えてんぞ 俺
And right after I managed
to save this life too...
せっかく拾った命なのにな
そうだ 拾った俺の命だ
だから―
That's right. I saved my life, so...
What's wrong with taking the easiest path,
the path that will let me live longer?
（スバル）
楽なほうに 生きやすいほうへ
それを目指して何が悪い
I'll decide how I use my life!
使い方は―
俺が決める！
You were too slow.
もたもたしすぎたのよ
やっと見つけた
I finally found you.
I won't let you get away.
もう絶対に逃がさない
I suppose you should stay back.
（ベアトリス）
下がるかしら
契約が生きている以上―
As long as my contract exists,
ベティーは お前が相手でも
手を抜かないのよ
I won't hold back, not even against you.
ベアトリス様こそ―
And you, Beatrice-sama, seem to forget
that we aren't in the mansion now.
ここが屋敷の中でないことを
お忘れでしょ
We're in the forest,
away from the forbidden library.
禁書庫から離れ
そして 森の中―
ラムから その男を守れる
自信がおありですか
Are you certain you can protect him from me?
Boing!
（スバル）びよーん
（ベアトリス）ああ…
Oh, yeah, I've always wanted to do that!
うん なかなか快感
Wh-Wh...
Wh-What are you doing!?
D-Do you want to die!?
何をしてやがるのよ！
おま… お前は
死にたいのかしら！
バカ言うんじゃねえよ
Don't be dumb.
I have absolutely zero desire to die.
死にたくなんか かけらもねえ
死ぬのなんか本当に
人生の最後に１回だけでいい
One death at the end of a long life
is more than enough for me.
That's how I really feel.
本気でそう思う
How brave of you.
（ラム）
いい度胸だわ
やっと観念したってこと？
Finally accepted your fate?
観念とは少し違うな
I wouldn't call it that.
If anything,
言うなれば
覚悟が決まったってとこか
I'd say I made up my mind.
悪かったな
俺がヘタレなせいで―
Sorry. I caused you guys a lot
of grief by being such a loser.
随分とお前たちを悲しませた
So you really do know
something about Rem!?
（ラム）
やっぱり レムのことを何か…
（スバル）
いいや 悪いけど
それは本気で分からない
No, sorry, but I honestly
don't know a thing.
正直 分かんないことだらけだ
Frankly, there's too much I still don't know.
But...
けど―
I've decided to learn more
about the things I don't know.
分かんねえことだらけなのを
知っていこうと そう思ったよ
How can you say that now?
いまさら 何を…
レムはもう死んでしまったの
Rem is already dead.
What good will learning
anything do now!?
いまさら 何かが分かったところで
何ができるっていうの！
I won't make any cool statements
about what I'll be able to do.
何かができるなんて―
かっちょいいことは
言えねえ
何もできなかった結果が
このザマだからな
After all, this happened
because I couldn't do anything.
説得力なんてゼロなのは
俺が一番分かってる
I know better than anyone
that my words hold no weight.
ただ 俺は覚えてんだ
But I still remember...
I know parts of you two
that you've forgotten!
お前らが忘れたお前らを
知っているんだ
What do you know about Rem and me!?
あなたに ラムとレムの
何が分かるっていうの！
You're right.
そうだな 俺は肝心なことは
何にも知らないまんまだ
I don't know anything that actually matters.
だけど―
But you don't know this either, do you!?
お前らだって知らないだろうが
Know what?
何を
That I love you guys!
俺が お前らを―
大好きだってことをだよ！
（スバル）てやーっ
（ベアトリス）あっ
Wait!
待って！
This is something only I can do!
俺にしかできないことだ！
I swear I'll kill you!
（ラム）
絶対に殺してやるー！
I swear I'll save you!
（スバル）
絶対 助けてやるー！
Natsuki Subaru's ReStart